taxmanagementindia.com 2010-11-22

# Privacy Policy

Please note that the practices of www.taxmanagementindia.com, with respect to data collected and used by [www.taxmanagementindia.com](http://www.taxmanagementindia.com/) in connection with this website are governed by this online privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") as amended from time to time. Please regularly review our Privacy Policy. If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should immediately discontinue use of the Site and the Products and Services enabled by the Site.

[www.taxmanagementindia.com](http://www.taxmanagementindia.com/) is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of its customers / clients / members and has taken all necessary and reasonable measures to protect the confidentiality of the customer information and its transmission through the world wide web and it shall not be held liable for disclosure of the confidential information when in accordance with this Privacy Commitment or in terms of the agreements, if any, with the Customers.

[www.taxmanagementindia.com](http://www.taxmanagementindia.com/) undertakes not to disclose the information provided by the member / visitor / client to any person, unless such action is necessary to:

·        Conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; 

·        Protect and defend [www.taxmanagementindia.com](http://www.taxmanagementindia.com/)'s or its Affiliates' rights, interests or property; 

·        Enforce the terms and conditions of the products or services; or 

·        Act to protect the interests of [www.taxmanagementindia.com](http://www.taxmanagementindia.com/), its Affiliates, or its members, constituents or of other persons.

[www.taxmanagementindia.com](http://www.taxmanagementindia.com/) will limit the collection and use of customer information only on a need-to-know basis to deliver better service to the members / clients. [www.taxmanagementindia.com](http://www.taxmanagementindia.com/) may use and share the information provided by the members / clients with its Affiliates and third parties for providing services and any service-related activities such as collecting subscription fees for such services, and notifying or contacting the members / clients regarding any problem with, or the expiration of, such services. 

Please note that any information you post to a public bulletin board, such as discussion Forums (the "Forums"), is available to all persons accessing that location, and your e-mail address may also be posted on these venues. The information you share, including your email address, would then be available to all persons accessing these venues, and such information may be read, collected or used by others for any purpose, including sending you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for any information you elect to submit in these venues or the use of such information. In addition, you should be aware that the Forums offer a service in which subscribers are e-mailed a copy of all messages posted to the Forums on a particular topic. Consequently, if you post a message to the Forums, your e-mail address will be sent to those subscribers who have indicated an interest in the topic of your message.

Some Products and Services allow the tracking of access to or use of Products and Services by users. For example, certain Products and Services allow document authors to restrict access to documents, track access to or use of those documents, or involve communications and transmission of data over the Internet to verify the authenticity of documents, authors and recipients. In many cases, this type of tracking will be obvious to you as a user of the Products and Services, and in others, the software and services license or terms of use, pop-up boxes, or email messages will inform you of these features and your options, such as disabling options.

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, and most Products and Services that include similar devices are typically initially activated to collect data. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. But, in case you choose not to accept cookies, certain web pages may not be accessible.
